[Lisa and Frank laugh]
-[Frank]  Ready?
-[Lisa]  Okay.
[playing guitar]
[laughs] Dad.
[inaudible]
[man yells]
[tires screeching]
-[engine revving]
-[men groaning]
One batch...
two batch.
Penny and dime.
-[man screaming]
-[bodies squelching]
[crowd cheering]
[man in Spanish] Here he comes!
[men laughing]
-[man 1] Welcome home.
-[man 2] The one that got away!
Screw you, Punisher, piece of shit!
[man 3] You're safe back in Mexico.
[man 4] Punisher comes to Juarez,
we'll kill his ass.
[woman] The last survivor of the cartel
deserves a reward.
[rap music playing]
[inaudible]
-[slow exhale]
-[gunshot]
[woman on PA in English]  Flight 1513
to Dublin, Ireland, boarding at Gate 31.
Again, that's Flight 1513
to Dublin at Gate 31.
Hey, it's Mickey.
Yeah, anyone else make it?
Oh, shit, I'm the only one left?
No, I'm good. I'm good.
Yeah, about to board.
Tell Dublin to get ready for a big party.
I'm on my way.
[Mickey groans]
[Mickey gasping]
[stammers, panting]
-Please don't--
-[Frank shushes]
You won. You... you killed everyone.
The bikers, the cartels,
the Kitchen Irish... they're all gone.
-Yeah. Yeah, almost.
-I get it.
An eye for an eye and all that.
-I got a family of my own.
-I don't.
For God's sake, man,
killing me is not gonna bring yours back.
-What does it change if I'm dead?
-Nothing.
-[man speaking indistinctly]
-[yells]
-Oh, God.
-[gagging]
[groaning]
-Jeez.
-[choking]
-[man 1] Can you believe that?
-[man 2] Get a room, you dirty bastards!
[woman on PA]  Flight 1513 to Dublin,
Ireland, is now boarding.
[theme music playing]
[grunting]
[indistinct chatter]
[Donny] Yo!
-Are you the new guy?
-Yeah. Uh, Donny Chavez.
[spits] All right, let's see how you do.
Come on.
[Lance whistles]
That's the gimp.
Don't worry about him. He ain't all there.
-[man 1] That's the shit.
-[man 2] Yeah, yeah.
Yo! Castiglione!
[men laugh]
Hey, dumbass... lunch time.
[men laughing]
-Retard loves that hammer.
-Yeah.
[men laughing]
[indistinct chatter]
-[yells]
-[children laugh]
[yelling]
[panting]
[car alarm wailing]
[neighbors conversing indistinctly]
[neighbor] The rice is ready!
[police siren wailing]
[neighbors conversing indistinctly]
[laughing]
-Hey, sleepyhead.
-[gasps softly]
-[car horns honking]
-[groans softly]
-[grunts]
-[Lance] This goddamn guy.
[Leo] He's crazy, Lance.
What are you gonna do?
Hey, what's the story with you, man?
Here early, here late.
You know if they don't ask you to work
extra, they don't pay you for it, right?
-[Paulie] Right?
-But you knew that, right?
You got a tongue in your head?
I don't know what your deal is, man.
I'm guessing, uh, "elevator don't go
up to the penthouse" type thing.
-[all laughing]
-Hey, whatever, right?
But this shit you do, that's hurting us.
Because of you,
we're getting less overtime.
Kick his ass, Lance.
Maybe he'd understand that.
Wise up, window licker.
-All right. All right.
-[Scut chuckles]
[men laugh]
-[Paulie] Shit, there go the PB and Js.
-There he is.
You don't want me for an enemy, man.
-[Scut] You gotta be kiddin'!
-[Leo] All this talk.
-Why don't we make it interesting?
-[Donny] Yo!
[stammers] I would whup your butt.
-Put money on it.
-All right.
-Fifty. Hundred.
-Oh, big talk. Big talk.
-Where you going?
-I'm gonna whup your ass.
[Leo] Easy money.
-[Lance] We'll see.
-Can I come?
-No room.
-[engine revving]
[tires screeching]
[grunts]
[exclaims]
This is high, man. Shit.
I'm Donny.
[sighs]
You can see forever up here, huh?
[grunting]
-This why you come up here?
-Hmm.
I come up here because no one else does.
Yeah.
[Frank sighs]
Pete, right?
Well, Pete, my grandma makes
the best sandwich in the five boroughs.
And you ain't gonna know that
unless you try one.
Come on, man. A man's gotta eat.
Especially the way you're throwing
that hammer. [chuckles]
Like Cool Hand Luke or something.
One-man chain gang.
You like that movie?
I take one of those sandwiches,
you stop talking?
[chuckles]
No promises.
Appreciate it.
You know...
everyone thinks you're a retard.
But I knew you wasn't.
Lance shouldn't have done that, man.
Everyone's just worried
about making money, that's all.
Shit, I could use the overtime myself.
I ain't worked in a while
and I gotta pay for my grandma's meds.
Those are some serious scars, man.
-That one a bullet hole?
-Yeah.
Shit.
You some sort of secret badass, Pete?
-Marine Corps.
-Yeah?
Yeah.
My pa was in the corps.
Yeah. In the 1/2 down in North Carolina.
He was like a superhero to me
or something.
Except they don't die, right?
[Frank mutters]
I'm sorry to hear that.
My pa, he served three tours.
Iraq twice, Afghanistan.
Then him and my ma were coming back
from a movie one night...
and got clipped by some kid
who had just passed his driving test.
I woke up the next morning,
they were just gone.
[sighs] You got family?
I was 12.
I had to come up here,
live with my grandma.
She's the only person I got left.
[Lisa]  Dad, look.
[voice fading] It's hard...
...took the fall
for some guys I hung out with...
but I never gave 'em up.
Semper Fi,  right?
Look, Donny. Thanks for the sandwich.
You know, I... appreciate that.
But I'm not looking for a pal, yeah?
Whatever it is you're looking for...
I'm not it.
Yeah... okay.
[Curtis]  There's a story I heard.
There's a soldier in a hole
and he can't get out,
so he yells for help.
An NCO comes by and says,
"Suck it up, son. Dig deep."
And gives the soldier a shovel.
The soldier does as he's told
and digs that hole deeper.
Then an officer comes by,
says, "Hell, son, use the tools
your NCO gave you."
And throws him a bucket.
So the trooper in the hole
uses the shovel to fill that bucket,
and the hole was deeper still, right?
Next up, psychiatrist comes by
and offers him drugs, tells him,
"This is gonna help you
forget about the hole."
And they do.
But then the pills run out.
Then a soldier comes up,
a guy just like him,
covered in mud and dirt,
and he hears the yells for help.
And that filthy soldier
jumps down in the hole, too.
And the kid, he freaks out.
"What are you doing?
Now we're both stuck in a hole."
And the filthy soldier just smiles...
and says, "Calm down, buddy.
I've been here before.
I know how to get out."
Got a couple of new faces in here today.
Welcome.
If you wanna talk, talk.
If you just wanna listen,
that's all good, too.
No judgment here,
just brothers and sisters who understand.
Only thing you've got to understand
is the world isn't changing.
The real persecuted minority
in this country today...
-is the Christian American patriot.
-Oh, here we go with the same bullshit.
You're blind, asshole.
Don't rag on me because I can see.
Kiss my ass, cracker.
Isaac, let O'Connor finish his piece,
the same way you do
when we get a blow-by-blow account
of your week's titty bar action.
-[all chuckle]
-Blow-by-blow is right.
We've got to do something
about the liberal, do-gooding assholes
who are running this country
into the ground.
The ones who want to take
our rights and our guns.
Anyone else got a take?
I just know that I fought for this country
and that it's got no place for me.
I don't know what the rules
are anymore, you know?
They're scared, man.
Because they aren't stupid.
They spent 15 years training an army
and then abandoned it on the streets.
A time is gonna come
when we have to defend ourselves
and... and put things back
to how they were.
You love this country,
you better be ready,
'cause the next war's gonna be here.
Blood will flow in the streets.
Sic semper tyrannis.
"Thus always to tyrants"?
You really think our governments
are tyrants, Lewis?
All I know is that we risked our lives
and we did terrible things...
and it meant nothing when we got home.
[indistinct chatter]
How you sleeping, Lewis?
Uh, better. I work a lot but, uh, better.
Group helps.
I've been reading a lot.
Perspective is good.
-Mmm-hmm.
-But...
the answers have to be your own.
You have to take an honest look in here
before we look anywhere else.
All right?
I'll see you next time.
Take care of yourself, Lewis.
[Frank] Was a good meeting, Curt.
There he is.
-You good?
-I'm copacetic, Frank. You?
Oh, yeah. Great.
-It's been a while.
-Yeah, I'm a slow reader.
Yeah.
-I appreciate it.
-Right.
I really enjoyed it.
Like I told Lewis...
books are great,
but they don't hold all the answers.
-Can I get some coffee?
-Help yourself.
Lewis drives a cab all night.
I don't think it's a coincidence, either.
I suspect he talks to himself
in the mirror.
And that's part of the problem, Frank.
Nobody wants to be themselves anymore.
Internet, social media,
goddamn talent shows for assholes...
Everybody wants to be somebody else.
Nobody...
is happy just to look at themselves
in the mirror, see themselves.
Then it means they don't have
to be responsible either.
So what about you, Frank?
What is it gonna take to make you happy?
Come on. "Happy"?
Happy is a kick in the balls
waiting to happen.
So you kick yourself in the balls first.
[scoffs]
That's crazy, Lieutenant.
[chuckles] Look...
you got half a life left to live,
my friend.
If you don't, you might as well be dead.
-Oh, I am dead, Curtis. You didn't hear?
-Bullshit.
You got a name, a passport,
as I recall...
Frank Castle's dead.
Pete Castiglione... he's got a life.
Anybody that had anything to do with what
happened to Maria and the kids are dead.
Mission accomplished.
And I don't have a problem with that.
Hell, if you would've asked me,
I woulda helped you.
I know that.
-I know you would have.
-But that was months ago.
Now the only person
you're punishing is yourself.
Thank you for the coffee.
Hey, Curt.
How often you think about it?
You know, the shit we did over there?
All the time.
But my conscience is clear.
Afghanistan... was different, you know?
-Different how?
-Just different.
Things we did, they...
they kinda got blurred.
What were you into, Frank?
-[sighs]
-You see, what worries me the most...
is that you've been in a hole so long
that it's become home.
Maybe that's where I'm supposed to be.
Do me a favor, Frank.
Don't be a wallowing asshole.
[scoffs]
Before I have to take this fake leg off
and beat you to death with it.
[both laughing]
Just imagine your tombstone.
"Frank Castle lose a ass-kicking contest
to a one-legged man."
-I'd do it.
-Yeah.
I'd actually kinda like to see that.
Take care of yourself, Curt.
ID, please?
-[phone ringing]
-[elevator dings]
-[Sam]  So who was this guy to you?
-[Dinah]  Ahmad Zubair was my partner.
He was taken from his home in Kandahar,
shot in the head,
-and buried in an unmarked grave.
-[Sam]  That's quite a story.
Doesn't bode well for me
as your newly assigned partner.
It's more than a story.
And Stein... we're not partners.
Sam.
-Stein sounds like a large beer glass.
-[scoffs]
And, uh, according to the assignments,
that's exactly what we are.
Partners, I mean.
Sure, you're the lead agent
with a nice office
and I'm the junior
with the shitty little desk outside,
but... partners nevertheless.
-Gotta earn my trust first.
-Yeah.
That's exactly what I have to do.
Your approval immediately being
the most important thing in my life.
Madani, you really think Wolf
is gonna let you run with all this?
I'm confident I can persuade the SAC
of the case's merits.
Well... I guess you are new here.
[knocking on door]
Morning, sir.
Back in the country three weeks,
and you already have a case for me.
I brought this one back
from Afghanistan with me, sir.
This man, Ahmad Zubair
of the Afghan National Police,
discovered United States soldiers
were trafficking heroin.
And they killed him for it.
Stein, give us the room.
Sir, uh, as Madani's new partner,
-shouldn't I--
-Close the door on your way out.
You're lucky, Madani.
A lot of people would give their left tit
for this job.
I was happy where I was... tits intact.
Others weren't.
The investigation you were pursuing
in Kandahar was deemed to serve no one.
Deemed by who?
Frankly, you must have
a guardian angel, Madani.
They pulled you out of there before
you did your career some real harm.
I guess you tick a lot of boxes,
because they didn't want
the poster girl embarrassing them.
[chuckles] Wow. That was sexist, racist,
and demeaning of my abilities
all in one sentence, sir. Bravo.
Well, sue me. It's your word against mine.
Kinda like your case here.
The US government gave Ahmad Zubair
our word, and it got him killed.
A place like this,
who knows what got him killed?
He could've been dirty.
I was pulled out of Afghanistan
'cause something stunk to high heaven
and I was close
to finding out exactly what.
And here you are.
Now, I like tenacious
and energetic, Madani.
I find it kinda hot in a woman.
But I will not stand for insubordinate.
Are we clear?
Ask your little buddy Stein about that.
Now, Kandahar is off-limits.
Otherwise, you can quit.
-You're the boss.
-Yes, I am.
[hammering]
-[grunting]
-[men conversing indistinctly]
[Leo] I need a drink.
-[Paulie] Murphy's?
-[Scut] Maybe Rhonda will be working.
Maybe this time you'll speak to her.
-Like she'd notice.
-Bite me, dipshit.
I could use a drink.
[Frank continues grunting]
Come on, Lance.
Let me come with you guys.
Look, first round's on me.
-[all exclaiming]
-All right.
-Yeah, sure.
-[chuckles]
Why not, huh? Why not?
[knocking on door]
-Good meeting with Wolf, huh?
-Peachy.
As your immediate junior
in the chain of command...
am I allowed to ask
how you're feeling about that?
How about you lay off
with the "junior" shit?
I can live without
your wiseass comments right now.
Not really sure what else I have to offer.
You know how I knew
Wolf wouldn't want your case?
You got me for a partner.
You're telling me this why?
You seem like a good person.
Someone with a career in the department
if you really want one.
[scoffs] What did you do to piss him off?
You gotta earn my trust first.
[chuckles softly]
So...
what now?
Now I want you to get me whatever we have
on a Marine Force Recon colonel
called Schoonover,
the explosion and drug bust
at the 41st Street docks last year,
and everything available
on one of his men,
Lieutenant Frank Castle.
The Punisher? He's dead.
Castle and Schoonover
served in Afghanistan, same unit,
then both are dead one day
and 20 miles apart...
right here in New York.
That strike you as a coincidence?
-You're gonna run with this anyway?
-Do you have a problem with that?
No.
I'm already on the shit pile.
Just surprised a hotshot like you
is so eager to join me there.
Rhonda!
Five more beers and...
and five more shots of that good stuff
for me and my new pals here. [laughs]
Last round, and then I'm closing up.
He pukes, you assholes are cleaning it up,
all right?
You hear that? Keep it together, Donny.
Hey. [clears throat]
I need to pull another job.
I got this... Gnucci loan shark.
This guy's up my ass.
Prick is threatening to break my legs,
take my car, the whole thing.
[chuckles]
-[sighs]
-Man, what were you thinking?
What were you thinking
taking money off those guys?
What'd you think was gonna happen?
You got something for me or not?
-[sighs] Thanks, Rhonda.
-Yeah.
Yeah, all right.
Just take it easy, man, okay? I'll, uh...
I'll call my cousin. All right?
See if he can hook us up again.
-Soon, Paulie. Soon.
-Yeah. Okay. All right. All right. Okay.
I'll call him tonight, all right?
-[Donny chuckles] Whoa.
-[Scut] Whoa!
[Leo] Keep it together, Donny.
-The state of this guy, man.
-[Leo] She's looking, man.
[Leo and Scut laughing]
Your check.
[scoffs]
Pay the lady.
What? You said you were buying, right?
[sighs]
Yeah. Yeah.
-[Paulie chuckles]
-All right.
-[Scut] Yeah!
-[Leo] Heck, yeah!
-[Leo] I knew you were buying.
-[Scut] Big bucks.
-Hey, sleepyhead.
-[Frank gasps softly]
-[Frank] Hey.
-Hi.
[Frank chuckles]
-What time is it?
-It's 10:30.
[Frank chuckles]
You needed your sleep.
Yeah.
There's plenty of time
now that you're home.
[gasps]
[sighs]
[Paulie] My cousin came through big time.
[Lance] All right. All right.
What's the job, huh?
[Paulie] It's a poker game. High stakes.
-Fifty, maybe even seventy grand.
-[Lance exhales heavily]
[Paulie] I know. I know.
They got a "no guns at the table" rule.
Except for one guard standing at the door.
We go in...
we take out the guard,
the two of us cover the room.
One of us scoops up the cash,
and one outside in the car.
[scoffs] What's the catch?
Why isn't someone hitting this every week?
[laughs] It's protected by the Gnuccis.
-[laughing]
-Are you crazy?
You want to hit an outfit game?
-I don't know, Paulie. Paulie, this is--
-[Paulie] Hey. Don't be a pussy.
And besides, I thought...
you'd like the idea of paying back
the Gnuccis' shylock with his own cash.
-Yeah, I do.
-There we go.
-I do.
-Attaboy. Attaboy.
-All right.
-[Frank sips loudly]
Who's that?
Look who it is...
-[Paulie sighs heavily]
-Captain Batshit.
Were you listening to us?
Hmm?
Everywhere I turn,
there you are, pissing me off.
Now, you...
you need to mind your own business.
[Paulie] Putting your nose
where it don't belong, huh?
What?
What? What do you wanna do?
Huh?
What do you wanna do?
Whoa, where you goin'? Where you goin'?
Oh, where you goin'?
You're gonna get hurt, gimp.
Oh.
Oh, you wanna do something
with that hammer?
Huh? You wanna... You wanna do something?
What do you wanna do? You wanna take me?
I'm right here.
I ain't going anywhere.
And I will mess you up
without breaking a sweat.
Are we clear on that? Huh?
Yeah, you better stay out of my way,
or that hammer's gonna find
a new home up your ass.
-[chuckles]
-Do you understand?
-[man in the distance] Yeah, that's it.
-Huh?
-[men shouting]
-[metal clanging]
-[man screaming]
-[metal clattering]
-[Lance] Shit!
-[men continue shouting]
[Scut groaning loudly]
[man] Call somebody. Hurry up!
[continues groaning]
Jesus! You can see the bone!
[man] All right. Call an ambulance.
You were in the Marines, right?
You must know first aid or field medicine
or something! Come on!
[Scut crying]
We gotta cancel tonight.
No, man.
My cousin will think we pussied out.
-[sighs]
-I thought you needed the money.
-I do.
-Then let's do it, huh?
We got nothing to worry about.
Don't worry.
-Hey. Hey, hey...
-[Paulie] Hmm?
-What about him?
-Him?
-You can't be serious.
-What? He's no virgin.
-Hey, Donny. Come here.
-[Paulie sighs]
[Donny clears throat]
-That was messed up, huh?
-Yeah, shitty luck. For him, for us.
Hey, look, we got a thing tonight.
Make us some real money.
But... Scut going down
has left us a man short.
I ain't gonna lie to you, Donny.
This ain't exactly... legal.
-You got the balls for it?
-Hey, man, I got plenty of balls.
I don't doubt it. So you in?
-No, man. I need to know more about it.
-[Paulie] Nah. You're in or you're not.
[Lance] Serious money, hour's work.
Huh? You'd be doing us a solid.
[sighs] Yeah.
-All right, I'll help you out.
-[Lance] All right.
All right. He's growing up, huh?
-One of the boys.
-He's growing up.
[Lance] All right,
help us clean this shit up.
All right, over here.
[sighs]
[Farah] Why is it that you resent
being home so much, do you think?
I resent being forced to come back.
I resent that no one is hiding that fact.
Mostly, I...
I resent that no one wants the truth.
I just want you to be sure
that this case of yours isn't just a way
to avoid dealing with losing someone
you were close to.
I didn't lose anyone. They killed him.
I told Ahmad he could trust us.
Told him he could trust me.
How much are you drinking these days?
[sighs] Jesus, Mom. Now and then.
Maybe more now I'm home and have access
to your $100 a bottle stuff.
I know your heart is in the right place,
but I don't need therapy.
Definitely not from you. No offense.
None taken.
That. That right there.
That is why therapy
would never work for me.
Talking to you is like...
It's like interviewing a suspect
you know has the answers
and just smiles in your face.
That's not about being a psychiatrist.
It's about being your mother.
[sighs]
Nice to have you back.
Nice to share this with you.
It's temporary.
Just till I find a place.
Every night, I drink a glass of wine
over dinner with your father.
He usually pours it for me.
And not once in almost 40 years
has he joined me.
His faith is as strong as my lack of it.
I sometimes ask him,
"How can a surgeon believe in God?"
He says he would go mad
if he couldn't see some kind
of guiding principle in the world.
I have faith in a system. Our system.
The one that took you and Dad in
and made you wealthy and respected.
This country gave us freedom.
But it's fragile. It needs protection.
Your father's faith in God doesn't mean
that he cannot see the flaws
in his religion.
Why don't you tell me what it is
you're trying to say, Mom?
This case of yours is heresy, Dinah.
You've been told as much.
What you're doing scares me.
I don't want to see your head on a plate.
[neighbors conversing indistinctly]
[sighs]
[chuckles]
Keep it runnin'.
Let's boogaloo.
-[Lance] Get up. Come on, move your ass!
-[man groans]
[Paulie] Nobody move! Nobody!
-Or you get what he got! Eyes down.
-[Lance] Stay down!
[Donny panting]
[Lance] Hey. Bag the cash!
-[Donny] Shit.
-[Lance] All right, listen up, fellas.
This is gonna go nice and easy.
We know none of you is packing.
So no heroics, huh?
You boys should leave while you can.
[Paulie] Shut up, greaseball,
or you'll get what he got.
-[Lance] Eyes on the table!
-Do you know whose game this is?
I guess not.
Otherwise you wouldn't be here.
[Paulie] Or maybe we don't give a shit
about you oily Gnucci   shitbags.
-You're all dead.
-[Lance] Come on, let's go.
-Let's go!
-[Paulie] Hurry up!
[Lance] Move. Move. Move. Move!
Let's go. Don't look at him!
Eyes on the table!
You got any sense, kid,
you'll drop that bag and walk away.
[Paulie] Don't speak again, asshole.
Or what?
Hurry up. We don't got all day!
Or we don't get shit!
Take every last one
of these shitbags' dollars! Hurry up!
What are you doing?
-[Lance] Kid, pick it up!
-[Donny] Shit.
Let's go!
Shit, you really screwed this up, Donald.
-[Paulie] We gotta cap 'em.
-[Lance] No! Come on.
-Get out of here. Move! Yo, move!
-[Donny] Shit.
-[Lance] Move!
-[Paulie] Come on.
[door opens]
-Hey, sleepyhead.
-[gasping] What?
-[sighs] Hey.
-Hi.
[chuckles] Yeah.
-What time is it?
-Mmm. It's 10:30.
[Frank chuckles]
You needed your sleep.
There's plenty of time
now that you're home.
I'm gonna go get breakfast.
-Okay.
No!
[breathing heavily and grunting]
[grunts and sighs]
-[grunting]
-Dad!
-[yelling]
-Dad, look!
-No!
-[children laughing]
[hammering continues]
[tires screeching]
[Donny] Shit. Shit. Shit. Shit. Shit.
-Give me the gun.
-[Donny] I made a mistake, man. I'm sorry.
[stammers] I didn't know whether to...
I figured...
I figured bring my license,
you know,
in case we got stopped by the cops.
To act normal, right?
And I'm sorry, Lance.
[groaning]
He's gotta disappear.
They're gonna look for him.
I wouldn't give you up. I promise.
The shit they'll do to you, man,
you'd be crazy if you didn't.
[Donny groans]
-We have to do this.
-[Donny whimpers]
-No.
-[Donny] No. No.
-He's gotta disappear.
-[breathing heavily]
-[snaps fingers] Start the mixer.
-Are we really doing this?
Start that thing now!
[Donny] Please.
[mixer whirring]
What the hell, huh?
-Let's work a little overtime.
-[Donny] No! No!
[Lance] Shit! Get him! Come on! Go! Go!
-[Donny panting]
-[Lance] Come on, get him!
-Move! Move, move!
-[Donny] Shit!
[Lance] Shit!
-Put it down.
-I'll run. I'll run. Just let me go.
-Can't happen, Donny.
-Just shoot him.
[panting]
-Forget it. I'll shoot him.
-No. No bullets!
[Donny grunting]
-[Lance grunts]
-[Donny groans]
[all grunting]
-Get him up!
-[Donny groaning] No!
[Lance] All right, let's go.
-[straining] No! No!
-[Leo] Ah, shit!
-Come on!
-[sobbing] No! No! No!
Lance, I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I won't say anything, man!
[sobbing]
No! [grunting]
No! No! No! No! No!
-Come on!
-[Donny] No!
[groans] No! No! No!
[gasping]
[sobbing] No!
Lance! No, please!
Lance! Turn it off!
Lance! Please!
You brought this on yourself!
-[Donny] Please! Help me!
-[Frank] Shut it off.
[Donny] Turn it off! Help!
[Leo] Hey... look, it's the gimp.
-[chuckles]
-[Donny] Lance!
Turn it off! [sobbing] No!
-Tonight just gets better and better.
-[screams]
-[grunting]
[Leo groans]
[Paulie groaning]
-[bone breaking]
-[Leo groaning]
[Tom Waits' "Hell Broke Luce" playing]
♪ I had a good home
But I left ♪
But I left, right, left ♪
-[yells]
-[screams]
♪ Bomb made me deaf ♪
[yells]
No, please! [screaming] Lance!
♪ Hell broke luce ♪
-[gun clicking]
-[Lance] Paulie!
[Paulie gasping]
Paulie, don't leave me!
[Lance grunting]
[groaning]
-[bone breaking]
-[Lance screams]
[groaning]
♪ Dig damn ditches
In the middle of the road ♪
♪ You pay a hundred dollars
Just for filling in the hole ♪
♪ Listen to the general
Every goddamn word ♪
♪ How many ways
Can you polish up a turd? ♪
♪ And left, right ♪
[Donny screaming]
♪ Left, right
Hell broke luce ♪
[Lance grunts] Oh, please.
Please, just let me go, man.
Take the money. Take the money, man.
You don't have to kill me over this.
It was him or us! [grunting]
Oh, God!
-Where did it go down?
-What?
-[grunts]
-[screams] God!
[crying] No!
-Talk.
-[whimpering]
-[screaming, sobs]
-[grunts]
Okay! Okay!
It's in the basement of a restaurant.
Linello's in Little Italy.
Okay. I told you. Ow!
[crying] No, no, no, no. I told you.
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna find a home for this.
-No!
-[yells]
[yells]
Help!
[gasping]
[car engine starts]
[tires screeching]
[Tony] No one sleeps
until we get these guys.
Start with this kid, Donald Chavez.
My guy in the precinct called
with an address in Queens.
He lives with his grandmother.
Do what you have to
to make him give up the others.
-Christ. Get the circuit breaker.
-[man 1] You got it.
-[gunshot]
-[man 2] Heads up!
-[rapid gunfire]
-[men shouting]
[men groaning]
-[gunfire resumes]
-[man 3 groans]
[Tony breathing heavily]
[Frank grunting]
-[indistinct chatter on radio]
-[sirens wailing]
-[Micro] Oh.
-[typing]
Oh.
Mmm-hmm...
Yeah, man.
[sighing]
[sighs]
Welcome back, Frank.
[dramatic music playing]